MARIE MOORE

FRONT E N D W E B DEVELOPER JAVASCRIPT REACT

CONTACT



07-49-66-88-83



marie.rodiet@gmail.com



77163 MORTCERF



ttps://marierodiet.github.io /portfolio/

HARD SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, SASS
- JAVASCRIPT, TYPESCRIPT
- REACT, REDUX
- FIGMA, WIREFRAME
- GIT
- TESTING, DEBUGGING
- RESPONSIVE APPS

LANGUAGES

English



French



Chinese



SOFT SKILLS

- Time Management
- Problem solving
- Teamwork
- Critical Thinking
- Adaptability

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I am actively looking for a position as a front end web developer in a company that will challenge me and bring me to the next level.

I am a self-motivated professional with a strong capacity for finding solutions, something I have learned through more than a decade of international life, first in China, then in the United States. The drive that led me to gain functional or native fluency in Chinese and English has also let me to pursue coding languages with the same passion. Put simply: I love communication and problem-solving in all its forms, whether that means with other people, or as a bridge between people and their technology. I am looking for a work environment that will challenge me in both wavs.

EDUCATION

Bachelor in React JS Front-End Web Developement

OPENCLASSROOMS (2021- September 2022)

Responsive Web Design

JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures

FREECODECAMP CERTIFICATIONS(2021-2022)

M.A French Literature

University of Oregon (2014-2016)

Bachelor English History and Literature

Université du Littoral Côte d'Opale (2007-2009)

University of Malta (2009-2010)

WORK EXPERIENCE

French Language Instructor, Eugene OR 2014-2016

I taught beginning and intermediate French to university undergraduates. I learned to become a motivator in language acquisition because so many of my students were taking French as a required course, rather than by choice. Sparking interest in my students made my work enjoyable and effective. I planned, prepared, and delivered lessons on all aspects of spoken and written French. I also provided feedback and found ways to relate to students from a variety of different cultural backgrounds.

Administrative Support Specialist, Lane Community College, Eugene OR 2017-2020

I provided administrative and translation support in French and Chinese for staff of the International Student Program.